ibmsecu.org 2015-03-19

# FACTS

                                                                                                                                     Rev. 12/2010
                               WHAT DOES IBM SOUTHEAST EFCU DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
 FACTS                         INFORMATION?
 Why?                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                               the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                               share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we
                               do.
 What?                         The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                               with us. This information can include:
                                 l Social Security number                                    l Transaction or loss history
                                 l Account balances                                          l Credit card or other debt
                                 l Payment history                                           l Wire transfer instructions
 How?                          All financial companies need to share Members' personal information to run their everyday business.
                               In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their Members' personal
                               information; the reasons IBM Southeast EFCU chooses to share; and whether you can limit this
                               sharing.
    Reasons we can share your personal information                           Does IBM Southeast EFCU              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                                            share?
 For our everyday business purposes -                                                          Yes                           No
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your
 account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes -                                                                  Yes                           Yes
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                             No                       We don't share
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                              Yes                           No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -                                              Yes                           Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                           Yes                           Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                             No                       We don't share
 To limit our                    l Call (800) 873-5100 or (561) 982-4700 - our menu will prompt you through your choice(s)
 sharing                         l Email us at: serviceplus@ibmsecu.org
                               Please note:
                               If you are a new Member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
                               notice. When you are no longer a Member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                               notice.
                               However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?                    Call (800) 873-5100 or (561) 982-4700 or email serviceplus@ibmsecu.org
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                         PRIV-MODEL 8/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                               2010.3/2905 2658137-010 Custom EPRV2905                           Page 1 of 2

 Page 2
 Who We Are
 Who is providing this notice?           IBM Southeast EFCU means IBM Southeast Employees' Federal Credit Union.
 What We Do
 How does IBM Southeast EFCU To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
 protect my personal                     security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
 information?                            safeguards and secured files and buildings.
 How does IBM Southeast EFCU We collect your personal information, for example, when you
 collect my personal information? l Open an account                                              l Make a wire transfer
                                           l Apply for a loan                                    l Show your government-issued ID
                                           l Give us your income information
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                         affiliates, or other companies.
 Why can't I limit all sharing?          Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                           l sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your
                                              creditworthiness
                                           l affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                           l sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                         See below for more on your rights under state law.
 What happens when I limit               Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
 sharing for an account I hold
 jointly with someone else?
 Definitions
 Affiliates                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                         non-financial companies.
                                           l Our affiliates include: Southeast Services Organization, Inc. (SESO)
                                               l Financial, insurance and survey companies
 Nonaffiliates                           Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                         non-financial companies.
                                           l IBM Southeast EFCU does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to
                                              you.
 Joint Marketing                         A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                         financial products or services to you.
                                           l IBM Southeast EFCU doesn't jointly market.
 Other Important Information
 For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Members. We will not share personal information with
 nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
 For California Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or
 for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with
 our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
 For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Members. We will not share personal information from deposit or
 share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
 For Vermont Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or
 for joint marketing - without your authorization, and we will not share personal information with affiliates about your
 creditworthiness without your authorization.
Privacy Model Disclosure                                                                                                 PRIV-MODEL 8/1/2010
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 2010                       2010.3/2905 2658137-010 Custom EPRV2905                           Page 2 of 2
